affiliates.de 2015-06-11

# 

## Privacy Policy

Data security is taken very seriously by Crobo GmbH. All personal information will be collected and used in accordance with data privacy laws. In the following privacy notice, we will clarify what information we will need for the registration and usage of crobo.com. 

### Personal Information for Identification

We ask for personal information if you wish to register as a user for crobo.com. The information needed includes an email address, first and last name, username, and password. The required fields will be highlighted with an asterisk. 

### Usage of the Personal Information

The information collected by Crobo GmbH will be exclusively used and saved for Crobo services. In this case, the personal information that has been collected will be only used for services that require that information in order to personalize that particular service. The compliance with these terms will be held by Crobo in a record. If you do not wish to comply with these terms, then our services will not be available to you. For the security of your data, every visit to our website will prompt the saving of the IP-address as well as date, time and the page visited. This information is strictly used for statistics and will be made anonymous when evaluated. Crobo GmbH saves personal data on a separate server. Your information will only be used for the reasons that have been made known. 

### Propagation of Information

Personal information, as explained in section 2, will be exclusively used by Crobo GmbH and only given to other companies which have complied with the terms you have agreed to. Furthermore, your data will not be given to third parties with the exception that the information is requested by a court or other governmental body and your written consent. For particular offers and deals, you have the opportunity to ask for advertisement materials. In this case, the transfer of data is necessary and it is made clear that you will have to agree to the terms. You can revoke your consent at any time by sending a letter to Crobo GmbH, Schwedter Str. 263, 10119 or in the form of an email to [info@crobo.com](mailto:info@covus.de). 

### Type of Evaluation

Crobo GmbH carries out analysis of usage patterns of their websites in order to continually better their services. These evaluations are carried out with information that has been made anonymous. The who, when and what offer will, in no way, be provided to our advertising partners with the exception that the transfer of information has been consented to. 

### Usage of Cookies

Cookies are small text files that regularly recognize a visitor to a site. Personal information can be taken from them, saved or forwarded. 

Cookies, which are used by Crobo GmbH or their marketing partners, are marked with a number which, other than to the online offers of Crobo GmbH, have utterly no meaning and cannot be traced back to any one individual or personal information. The data can also not be used to identify you as a visitor of the website. These cookies help us to analyze how you use and interact with our website, allowing us to improve the content of our offers and meet your needs better. 

You can activate or completely/partially deactivate cookies in your browser if you wish to not take advantage of them. To do that, please look at your individual browser settings. 

Due to technical reasons, it is not possible to create posts in the online forum of Crobo GmbH if you do not allow cookies on your computer. However, you can choose to delete the cookies automatically upon leaving the forum by clicking “Logout” in the top right of the page. We recommend that you use the “Logout” option if other individuals have access to your computer. 

### Erasure of Personal Data

Your consent in relation to the collection and saving of your personal data by Crobo GmbH can be revoked at any time by sending a letter to Crobo GmbH, Schwedter Str. 263, 10119 Berlin or in the form of an email to [info@crobo.com](mailto:info@covus.de). 

### Further Information on Data Privacy

Please take notice that personal information that you make available online (such as in a chat room, per email or in forums) can be collected by others and used. It is possible that you may receive unwanted messages if you post personal information in areas which are accessible by the public. That is why we recommend that you go about your business with care and with responsibility when online and that, under no circumstance, should you share your password or login information. 

### Giveaways and Contests

In order to take part in a contest or giveaway, the username and/or complete name (first and last name) and a valid email address is required. In the case of a prize being won, it is possible that we will contact you per email and use your address for the purpose of delivery. 

Your data will be saved and used to the extent of the contest or giveaway (to alert and notify the winner) by Crobo GmbH, the owner and operator of crobo.com, up until the end of the giveaway or contest. 

After the contest or giveaway has ended, your data will no longer be used by Crobo GmbH and will be deleted. 

Removing your data, as stated in section 6, is also possible at any time for contests and giveaways. However, please keep in mind that if you delete your information, your participation in the contest or giveaway, as well as your opportunity to win any sort of prize, may lead to certain restrictions or may be no longer possible. 

### Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics – a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “Cookies”, text files that can be saved on your computers and make it possible to analyze your usage of a website. The information provided by cookies and your usage of the website are taken and saved on a server in the United States. If a proxy server is used in accessing this website, your IP address will be shortened by Google within the participating members of the European Union or in other states which are within the European economic area. Only in exceptional cases will the complete IP address sent to a server by Google in the United States and shortened there. By order of the operators of this website, Google will use this information in order to analyze your usage of the site in order to create reports about website activity as well as the usage of the site and internet usage of connected services. The IP address that is used by Google Analytics from your browser will not be used in conjunction with other information from Google. You can prevent the saving of cookies through a specific setting in your browser – but we must forewarn you, that if this is the case, you may not be able to use all of the functions of this website. Moreover, you can prevent Google from using cookies to analyze your usage of the site by going to the following link and installing the available browser plugin. You can find more information here and here (miscellaneous information in regards to Google Analytics and information privacy). We would like to point out that this website utilizes the addition Google Analytics code “gat_anonymizelp();”, in order to allow anonymized IP addresses (aka – IP Masking). 

### Right to Modify

Crobo GmbH has the right to change the information privacy policy in accordance with the law at any time.

## Polityka prywatności

Data security is taken very seriously by Covus Crobo GmbH. All personal information will be collected and used in accordance with data privacy laws. In the following privacy notice, we will clarify what information we will need for the registration and usage of crobo.com. 

### Personal Information for Identification

We ask for personal information if you wish to register as a user for crobo.com. The information needed includes an email address, first and last name, username, and password. The required fields will be highlighted with an asterisk. 

### Usage of the Personal Information

The information collected by Covus Crobo GmbH will be exclusively used and saved for Covus services. In this case, the personal information that has been collected will be only used for services that require that information in order to personalize that particular service. The compliance with these terms will be held by Covus in a record. If you do not wish to comply with these terms, then our services will not be available to you. For the security of your data, every visit to our website will prompt the saving of the IP-address as well as date, time and the page visited. This information is strictly used for statistics and will be made anonymous when evaluated. Covus Crobo GmbH saves personal data on a separate server. Your information will only be used for the reasons that have been made known. 

### Propagation of Information

Personal information, as explained in section 2, will be exclusively used by Covus Crobo GmbH and only given to other companies which have complied with the terms you have agreed to. Furthermore, your data will not be given to third parties with the exception that the information is requested by a court or other governmental body and your written consent. For particular offers and deals, you have the opportunity to ask for advertisement materials. In this case, the transfer of data is necessary and it is made clear that you will have to agree to the terms. You can revoke your consent at any time by sending a letter to Covus Crobo GmbH, Schwedter Str. 263, 10119 or in the form of an email to [info@covus.de](mailto:info@covus.de). 

### Type of Evaluation

Covus Crobo GmbH carries out analysis of usage patterns of their websites in order to continually better their services. These evaluations are carried out with information that has been made anonymous. The who, when and what offer will, in no way, be provided to our advertising partners with the exception that the transfer of information has been consented to. 

### Usage of Cookies

Cookies are small text files that regularly recognize a visitor to a site. Personal information can be taken from them, saved or forwarded. 

Cookies, which are used by Covus Crobo GmbH or their marketing partners, are marked with a number which, other than to the online offers of Covus GmbH, have utterly no meaning and cannot be traced back to any one individual or personal information. The data can also not be used to identify you as a visitor of the website. These cookies help us to analyze how you use and interact with our website, allowing us to improve the content of our offers and meet your needs better. 

You can activate or completely/partially deactivate cookies in your browser if you wish to not take advantage of them. To do that, please look at your individual browser settings. 

Due to technical reasons, it is not possible to create posts in the online forum of Covus Crobo GmbH if you do not allow cookies on your computer. However, you can choose to delete the cookies automatically upon leaving the forum by clicking “Logout” in the top right of the page. We recommend that you use the “Logout” option if other individuals have access to your computer. 

### Erasure of Personal Data

Your consent in relation to the collection and saving of your personal data by Covus Crobo GmbH can be revoked at any time by sending a letter to Covus Crobo GmbH, Schwedter Str. 263, 10119 Berlin or in the form of an email to [info@covus.de](mailto:info@covus.de). 

### Further Information on Data Privacy

Please take notice that personal information that you make available online (such as in a chat room, per email or in forums) can be collected by others and used. It is possible that you may receive unwanted messages if you post personal information in areas which are accessible by the public. That is why we recommend that you go about your business with care and with responsibility when online and that, under no circumstance, should you share your password or login information. 

### Giveaways and Contests

In order to take part in a contest or giveaway, the username and/or complete name (first and last name) and a valid email address is required. In the case of a prize being won, it is possible that we will contact you per email and use your address for the purpose of delivery. 

Your data will be saved and used to the extent of the contest or giveaway (to alert and notify the winner) by Covus Crobo GmbH, the owner and operator of crobo.com, up until the end of the giveaway or contest. 

After the contest or giveaway has ended, your data will no longer be used by Covus Crobo GmbH and will be deleted. 

Removing your data, as stated in section 6, is also possible at any time for contests and giveaways. However, please keep in mind that if you delete your information, your participation in the contest or giveaway, as well as your opportunity to win any sort of prize, may lead to certain restrictions or may be no longer possible. 

### Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics – a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “Cookies”, text files that can be saved on your computers and make it possible to analyze your usage of a website. The information provided by cookies and your usage of the website are taken and saved on a server in the United States. If a proxy server is used in accessing this website, your IP address will be shortened by Google within the participating members of the European Union or in other states which are within the European economic area. Only in exceptional cases will the complete IP address sent to a server by Google in the United States and shortened there. By order of the operators of this website, Google will use this information in order to analyze your usage of the site in order to create reports about website activity as well as the usage of the site and internet usage of connected services. The IP address that is used by Google Analytics from your browser will not be used in conjunction with other information from Google. You can prevent the saving of cookies through a specific setting in your browser – but we must forewarn you, that if this is the case, you may not be able to use all of the functions of this website. Moreover, you can prevent Google from using cookies to analyze your usage of the site by going to the following link and installing the available browser plugin. You can find more information here and here (miscellaneous information in regards to Google Analytics and information privacy). We would like to point out that this website utilizes the addition Google Analytics code “gat_anonymizelp();”, in order to allow anonymized IP addresses (aka – IP Masking). 

### Right to Modify

Covus Crobo GmbH has the right to change the information privacy policy in accordance with the law at any time.
